_Press enter to begin your search_

### **Privacy Policy**

**Introduction**  
Transdev North America, Inc. (“Transdev,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) respects the privacy of your information. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard the information you provide to us in using our websites, mobile applications (collectively, “Sites”), and the services provided through our Sites (collectively, “Services”).

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we do, we will post an amended version on this webpage. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically.

This Privacy Policy covers the following topics:

1. [Information We Collect Online](#section1)
2. [How We Use Your Information](#section2)
3. [How We Share Your Information](#section3)
4. [Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies](#section4)
5. [“Do Not Track” Signals](#section5)
6. [Choices About Your Personally Identifiable Information](#section6)
7. [Security](#section7)
8. [Third Party Links](#section8)
9. [Children’s Privacy](#section9)
10. [Your State Privacy Rights and Additional Disclosures](#section10)
11. [Notice to California Residents](#section11)
12. [Accessibility](#section12)
13. [How to Contact Us](#section13)

#### 1\. Information We Collect Online

We collect Personally Identifiable Information from you through your use of the Sites and Services. “Personally Identifiable Information” is individually identifiable information about an individual consumer that we collect online and that we maintain in an accessible form. This Privacy Policy is subject to prospective change at any time, and your use of the Service indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use. We collect the following types of Personally Identifiable Information:

**Information You Provide**  
We may collect the following Personally Identifiable Information that you voluntarily provide to us in using our Sites and Services:

* _Contact Us._ When you contact us online, we collect your name, email address, company name and any Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to provide to us in your message.
* _Mobile Applications._ If you register for an account on our My Transit Manager, Transdev Connect, MobiMe, GoMobile, or our other mobile applications, you will provide us with your name, email address, telephone number, geolocation data, and you will create a password. If you use our mobile applications, you will provide us with your geolocation data (regional and precise). Please note that if you are user of the Transdev Connect Service, no mobile information is shared with third parties or affiliates for marketing or promotional purposes, and any references to such sharing in this Privacy Policy do not apply to the Transdev Connect Services.
* _Register as an Approved Vendor._ As part of our Transdev Vendor Registration System, you will provide us with your name, email address, telephone number, mailing address, title, EIN number, ethnicity, gender, professional information, military/veteran status, and vendor/company information.
* _Apply for a Job._ If you wish to apply for a job on our career portal, you will create a profile via LinkedIn or provide us with your name, email address, and creating a password. You may also choose to upload your resume. We use Recruit Rooster and JobVite to facilitate this process. Please review [Recruit Rooster’s privacy policy here](https://recruitrooster.com/privacy-terms/), and [JobVite’s privacy notice here](https://www.employinc.com/privacy/). If you wish to receive email alerts about new job openings through our Talent Network, you will provide us with your email address or log in via LinkedIn.
* _Signup for Employee News Updates._ Current Transdev employees that wish to receive employee news updates to their inbox will provide us with their email address.

**Information as You Navigate Our Sites**  
We automatically collect certain Personally Identifiable Information through your use of the Sites and Services, such as the following:

* _Usage Information._ For example, the pages on the Sites you access, the frequency of access, and what you click on while on the Sites.
* _Device Information._ For example, hardware model, operating system, application version number, and browser.
* _Mobile Device Information._ Aggregated information about whether the Site is accessed via a mobile device or tablet, the device type, and the carrier.
* _Location Information._ Location information from Site visitors on a city-regional basis.

**Third Party Information**  
In some cases, we may receive certain Personally Identifiable Information from you about a third party. For example, as part of our vendor registration process, you may provide the name, email address, and telephone number of a third party. If you submit any Personally Identifiable Information about another individual to us, you are responsible for making sure you have the authority to do so and to allow us to use their Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### 2\. How We Use Your Information

We use the Personally Identifiable Information we collect to provide the Services to you, to improve our Sites and Services, and to protect our legal rights. In addition, we may use the Personally Identifiable Information we collect to:

* Process your account registration;
* Review your job application;
* Review your vendor application;
* Email you;
* Contact you regarding our products and services that we feel may be of interest to you;
* Communicate with you about our Sites or Services or to inform you of any changes to our Sites or Services;
* Provide support;
* Maintain and improve our Sites and Services;
* Protect the security and integrity of our Sites and Services;
* Investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our [Terms of Use](https://transdevna.com/terms/), and to otherwise fulfill our legal obligations;
* Monitor compliance with and enforce this Privacy Policy and any other applicable agreements and policies;
* Defend our legal rights and the rights of others;
* Fulfill any other purposes for which you provide it, or any other purpose we deem necessary or appropriate;
* Efficiently maintain our business; and
* Comply with applicable law.

#### 3\. How We Share Your Information

We may share the Personally Identifiable Information we collect from you in the following ways:

* With vendors who perform data or Site-related services on our behalf (e.g., email, hosting, maintenance, backup, analysis, etc.);
* With vendors to prepare, deploy and analyze advertising content;
* To the extent that we are required to do so by law;
* In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
* To establish, exercise, or defend our or a third party’s legal rights, including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention;
* With any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that Personally Identifiable Information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that Personally Identifiable Information;
* With any other person or entity as part of any business or asset sale, equity transaction, merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, or in preparation for any of these events;
* With any other person or entity where you consent to the disclosure; and
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the Personally Identifiable Information or for any other purpose we deem necessary, including to protect the health or safety of others.

As previously noted, if you are user of the Transdev Connect Service, no mobile information is shared with third parties or affiliates for marketing or promotional purposes.

#### 4\. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

**How We Use Cookies**  
Like many other companies, we use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as pixels and web beacons) (collectively, “Cookies”). Cookies are small files of information that are stored by your web browser software on your computer hard drive, mobile or other devices (e.g., smartphones or tablets).

We use Cookies to:

* Estimate audience size and usage patterns;
* Understand and save your preferences for future visits, allowing us to customize the Sites and Services to your individual needs;
* Advertise new content and services that relate to your interests;
* Keep track of advertisements and search engine results;
* Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions to resolve issues and offer better site experiences and tools in the future; and
* Recognize when you return to the Sites.

We set some Cookies ourselves, while separate entities set other Cookies. We use Cookies other entities set to provide us with useful information, to help us improve our Sites and Services, to conduct advertising, and to analyze the effectiveness of advertising. For example, we use Cookies from Google and other similar companies.

As previously noted, if you are user of the Transdev Connect Service, no mobile information is shared with third parties or affiliates for marketing or promotional purposes.

**How You Can Opt Out of Cookies**

_Your Preferences_  
When you first visit our Site, we will present you with a banner which offers you choices about whether to accept or reject cookies or tracking technologies of different types. If you wish to change your preferences, you can do so by clicking here:  
Cookie Settings  
This will allow you to change your preferences on Transdevna.com. If you wish to change your preferences on one of our other Sites, you can do so by clicking on the “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information” link included in the footer of that Site.

_Browser Settings_  
You can block Cookies by changing your Internet browser settings to refuse all or some Cookies. If you choose to block all Cookies (including essential Cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the Site.

You can find out more about Cookies and how to manage them by visiting [www.AboutCookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

_Platform Controls_  
You can opt out of Cookies set by Google by following the instructions found at this link: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/).

_Advertising Industry Resources_  
You can understand which entities have currently enabled Cookies for your browser or mobile device and how to opt out of some of those Cookies by accessing the [Network Advertising Initiative’s website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s website](http://optout.aboutads.info/). For more information on mobile specific opt-out choices, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Mobile Choices website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices).

Please note these opt-out mechanisms are specific to the device or browser on which they are exercised. Therefore, you will need to opt out on every browser and device that you use.

**Google Analytics**  
We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses Cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with the Sites and Services, compile reports on their activity, and provide other services related to their activity and usage. The technologies used by Google may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a returning visitor, and any referring website. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to [Google’s privacy policies](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en). To learn more about Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt out of tracking of analytics by Google, [click here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).

**Google reCAPTCHA**  
We use Google reCAPTCHA, a free service provided by Google, Inc., to protect our Sites from spam and abuse. Google reCAPTCHA uses advanced risk analysis techniques to decipher humans and bots. Google reCAPTCHA works differently depending on what version is deployed. For example, you may be asked to check a box indicating that you are not a robot or Google reCAPTCHA may detect abusive traffic without user interaction. Google reCAPTCHA works by transmitting certain types of information to Google, such as the referrer URL, IP address, visitor behavior, operating system information, browser and length of the visit, cookies, and mouse movements. Your use of Google reCAPTCHA is subject to Google’s [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Terms of Service](https://policies.google.com/terms). More information as to Google reCAPTCHA and how it works is [available here](https://developers.google.com/recaptcha).

#### 5\. Universal Opt-Out Mechanisms

The Sites recognize the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”) signal. If you are using a browser setting or plug-in that sends an opt-out preference signal to each website you visit, we will treat that as a valid request to opt out. To download and use a browser supporting the GPC browser signal, click here: [https://globalprivacycontrol.org/orgs](https://globalprivacycontrol.org/orgs). If you choose to use the GPC signal, you will need to turn it on for each supported browser or browser extension you use.

Some internet browsers incorporate a “Do Not Track” feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. Given that there is not a uniform way that browsers communicate the “Do Not Track” signal, the Sites do not currently interpret, respond to, or alter their practices when they receive “Do Not Track” signals.

#### 6\. Choices About Your Personally Identifiable Information

**Review and Request Changes to Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
You may use your account to access, correct, or view certain Personally Identifiable Information we have collected and which is associated with your account. To review or request changes to any of your Personally Identifiable Information, please contact us at [infoUS@transdev.com](mailto:infoUS@transdev.com).

**Marketing Communications**  
To unsubscribe from our marketing emails, please click the unsubscribe link included in the footer of our emails. You also may submit a request to us at [infoUS@transdev.com](mailto:infoUS@transdev.com).

#### 7\. Security

We maintain commercially reasonable security measures to protect the Personally Identifiable Information we collect and store from loss, misuse, destruction, or unauthorized access. However, no security measure or modality of data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. Although we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot guarantee absolute security.

#### 8\. Third Party Links

The Sites and Services may contain links that will let you leave the Sites and Services and access another website. Linked websites are not under our control. Except as stated below, this Privacy Policy applies solely to Personally Identifiable Information that is acquired by us on our Sites and Services. We accept no responsibility or liability for these other websites.

#### 9\. Children’s Privacy

The Sites and Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under 13.

#### 10\. Your State Privacy Rights and Additional Disclosures

Depending on the state in which you reside, you may have certain privacy rights regarding your Personally Identifiable Information. If you are a California resident, please see our “Notice to California Residents” section below. For other state residents, your privacy rights may include (if applicable):

* The right to confirm whether or not we are processing your Personally Identifiable Information and to access such Personally Identifiable Information and the categories of Personally Identifiable Information we are processing or have processed;
* The right to obtain a copy of your Personally Identifiable Information that we collected from and/or about you in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format that allows you to transmit the information to another controller without hindrance, where the processing is carried out by automated means;
* The right, at our option, to obtain a list of specific third parties, other than natural persons, to which we have disclosed your Personally Identifiable Information or any Personally Identifiable Information;
* The right to obtain a list of categories of third parties to which we have disclosed your Personally Identifiable Information;
* The right to delete Personally Identifiable Information that we collected from and/or about you, subject to certain exceptions;
* The right to correct inaccurate Personally Identifiable Information that we maintain about you, subject to certain exceptions;
* The right, if applicable, to opt out of the processing of your Personally Identifiable Information for purposes of (1) targeted advertising; (2) the “sale” of your Personally Identifiable Information (as that term is defined by applicable law); and (3) profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you;
* If we are required by applicable law to obtain your consent to process sensitive Personally Identifiable Information, the right to withdraw your consent; and
* The right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for the exercise of your privacy rights.

While we do not “sell” Personally Identifiable Information as that term may be commonly interpreted, depending on how the applicable privacy law defines a “sale,” we may sell Personally Identifiable Information to third parties if you are using certain applications or visiting certain websites. For instance, if you are a resident of Colorado or Connecticut, our use of cookies and tracking technologies constitutes a sale of Personally Identifiable Information to third-party advertisers. We also use cookies and other tracking to display advertisements about our products to you on nonaffiliated websites, applications, and online services. This is “targeted advertising” under applicable privacy laws. We do not use Personally Identifiable Information for profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning individuals. Further, as previously noted, if you are user of the Transdev Connect Service, no mobile information is shared with third parties or affiliates for marketing or promotional purposes.  
To exercise your rights, please submit a request through our interactive webform available here, by emailing us at infoUS@transdev.com, or by calling us toll free at 1-800-225-8880. If legally required, we will comply with your request upon verification of your identity and, to the extent applicable, the identity of the individual on whose behalf you are making such request. To do so, we will ask you to verify data points based on information we have in our records. If you are submitting an opt-out request on behalf of another individual, please use the same contact methods described above. We will process authorized agent requests in accordance with applicable law. If we refuse to take action regarding your request, you may appeal our decision through our interactive webform available here, by emailing us at infoUS@transdev.com, by calling us toll free at 1-800-225-8880, or by replying to the email you received from us in response to your request. If you would like to opt out of targeted advertising, you may alter your cookie preferences as described herein.

**Notice to Nevada Residents**

Nevada law allows Nevada residents to opt out of the sale of certain types of Personally Identifiable Information. Subject to several exceptions, Nevada law defines “sale” to mean the exchange of certain types of Personally Identifiable Information for monetary consideration to another person. We do not currently sell Personally Identifiable Information as defined in the Nevada law. However, if you are a Nevada resident, you still may submit a verified request to opt out of sales and we will record your instructions and incorporate them in the future if our policy changes. You may send opt-out requests to infoUS@transdev.com.

#### 11\. Notice to California Residents

The California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020 (“CCPA”), requires that we provide California residents with a privacy policy that contains a comprehensive description of our online and offline practices regarding the collection, use, sale, sharing, and retention of personal information and of the rights of California residents regarding their personal information. This section of the Privacy Policy is intended solely for, and is applicable only as to, California residents. If you are not a California resident, this section does not apply to you and you should not rely on it.

The CCPA defines “personal information” to mean information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular California resident or household. Personal information does not include publicly available, deidentified or aggregated information or lawfully obtained, truthful information that is a matter of public concern. For purposes of this “Notice to California Residents” section we will refer to this information as “Personal Information.”

The CCPA, including the consumer rights described in this section, however, does not apply to any protected health information that we in our capacity as a business associate governed by the privacy, security, and breach notification rules issued by the United States Department of Health and Human Services established pursuant to the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (“HIPAA”) and the Health Information Technology for Economic and Clinical Health Act. We will use that information only for the purposes for which we were engaged by the HIPAA covered entity.

If you are a California resident and a current or former employee, job applicant, or independent contractor of ours, please see our [privacy notice available here](https://transdevna.com/california-employee-privacy-policy/) for more information on our collection and use of your Personal Information in that capacity.

**Notice at Collection of Personal Information**  
We currently collect and, in the 12 months prior to the Last Updated Date of this Privacy Policy, have collected the following categories of Personal Information:

* Identifiers (name, alias, postal address, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, Medicaid IDs)
* Unique personal identifiers (device identifier; cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers, or other similar technology; customer number, unique pseudonym, or user alias; telephone numbers, or other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers that can be used to identify a particular consumer or device)
* Telephone number
* Signature
* Physical characteristics or description 
* Bank account number (if paying by check)
* Credit and debit card number 
* Insurance policy number (for liability claims purposes)
* Other financial information (Clipper card number)
* Medical information (e.g., medical equipment needed to travel)
* Insurance policy number or subscriber identification number (for liability claims purposes)
* Any unique identifier used by health insurer to identify consumer
* Any information in the consumer’s application and claims history, including appeals records, if information is linked or reasonably linkable to consumer or household, including via device, by business or service provider
* Internet or other electronic network activity information (browsing history; search history; and information regarding consumer’s interaction with website, application, or advertisement)
* Geolocation data
* Commercial information (records of personal property (for liability claims purposes), products or services purchased, obtained, or considered; other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies)
* Professional or employment-related information (e.g., company name, title)
* Biometric information (imagery of face, voice recordings)
* Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (race, color, sex/gender (including pregnancy, childbirth, breastfeeding and/or related medical conditions), gender identity/expression, age (40 and older), religion (including religious dress and grooming practices), national origin, disability (mental and physical including HIV/AIDS, cancer, and genetic characteristics), citizenship status, marital status, medical condition (genetic characteristics, cancer or a record or history of cancer), military or veteran status, status as a victim of domestic violence, assault or stalking, request for family care leave, request for leave for an employee’s own serious health condition, and retaliation for reporting patient abuse in tax-supported institutions)
* Audio, electronic, visual, or similar information
* Inferences drawn from above information to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes

We collect Personal Information directly from California residents and from third parties (e.g., client registration, medical professionals identified by applicants/riders), logistics platforms (e.g., transportation management system), cloud-based offerings and services, social media networks, payment processors, medical assistance transportation programs, data analytics providers, government entities (e.g., public transportation agencies), and operating systems and platforms. We do not collect all categories of Personal Information from each source.

In addition to the purposes stated above in the Section “How We Use Your Personally Identifiable Information” we currently collect and have collected the above categories of Personal Information for the following business or commercial purposes:

* Auditing related to counting impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards
* Helping to ensure security and integrity to the extent the use of the consumer’s Personal Information is reasonably necessary and proportionate for these purposes
* Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality
* Short-term, transient use
* Performing services, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing analytic services,  or providing similar services
* Providing advertising and marketing services
* Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration
* Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us
* Advancing our commercial or economic interests

**Sale, Sharing, and Disclosure of Personal Information**  
The following table identifies the categories of Personal Information that we sold or shared to third parties in the 12 months preceding the Last Updated Date of this Privacy Policy and, for each category, the category of third parties to whom we sold or shared Personal Information:

| **Categories of Personal Information** | **Category of Third Parties** |
| --- | --- |
| Internet Protocol addressCookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers, or other similar technology; customer number, unique pseudonym, or user alias<br><br>Internet or other electronic network activity information (browsing history; search history; and information regarding consumer’s interaction with website, application, or advertisement)<br><br>Geolocation data (regional; city/state) | Data analytics providers (e.g., Google Analytics) |

We sold or shared Personal Information to third parties for the following business or commercial purposes:

* Auditing related to counting impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning
* Providing advertising and marketing services
* Advancing our commercial or economic interests

As previously noted, if you are user of the Transdev Connect Service, no mobile information is shared with third parties or affiliates for marketing or promotional purposes.

The following table identifies the categories of Personal Information that we disclosed for a business purpose in the 12 months preceding the Last Updated Date of this Privacy Policy and, for each category, the categories of recipients to whom we disclosed Personal Information:

| **Categories of Personal Information** | **Categories of Recipients** |
| --- | --- |
| Name; alias; postal address; email address | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Payment processors  <br>– Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Customer engagement platforms (e.g., Twilio)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers)  <br>– Telecommunications vendors (e.g., ShoreTel) |
| Online identifier; account name | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers)  <br>– Telecommunications vendors (e.g., ShoreTel) |
| Customer number, unique pseudonym, or user alias; telephone numbers or other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers that can be used to identify a particular consumer or deviceTelephone number | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Payment processors  <br>– Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Customer engagement platforms (i.e., Twilio)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers)  <br>– Telecommunications vendors (e.g., ShoreTel) |
| Signature | – Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Physical characteristics or description | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers)  <br>– Telecommunications vendors (e.g., ShoreTel) |
| Bank account number; credit and debit card number | – Payment processors (e.g., Payeezy)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers)  <br>– Telecommunications vendors (e.g., ShoreTel) |
| Medical information | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Insurance policy number or subscriber identification number; any unique identifier used by health insurer to identify consumerAny information in the consumer’s application and claims history, including appeals records, if information is linked or reasonably linkable to consumer or household, including via device, by business or service provider | – Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk, Ecolane)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Information regarding consumer’s interaction with website, application, or advertisement | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Customer engagement platforms (i.e., Twilio) |
| Geolocation data (regional; city/state) | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Customer engagement platforms (i.e., Twilio)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers)  <br>– Telecommunications vendors (e.g., ShoreTel) |
| Geolocation data (precise) | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities) |
| Records of personal property | – Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered; other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Payment processors (e.g., JD Edwards, BottomLine)  <br>– Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities) |
| Professional or employment-related information | – Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Imagery of face; voice recordings | – Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Vendor (Lytx)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Race; color; sex/gender (including pregnancy, childbirth, breastfeeding and/or related medical conditions); gender identity/expression; age (40 and older) | – Claims service providers (e.g., Sedgwick)  <br>– Government entities  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Disability (mental and physical including HIV/AIDS, cancer, and genetic characteristics); medical condition (genetic characteristics, cancer or a record or history of cancer); marital status; military or veteran status | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Status as a victim of domestic violence, assault, or stalking | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Audio, electronic, visual, or similar information | – Call center software providers (e.g., Genesys/Packet Fusion)  <br>– Cloud-based service providers (e.g., Web Risk)  <br>– Vendor (Lytx)  <br>– Entities involved in liability claims (e.g., law firms, surveillance, insurance brokers, insurance carriers) |
| Inferences drawn from above information to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes | – Transportation providers  <br>– Clients (e.g., state authorities) |

We disclosed Personal Information for the following business or commercial purposes:

* Helping to ensure security and integrity
* Debugging to identify and repair errors
* Short-term, transient use
* Performing services
* Providing advertising and marketing services
* Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration
* Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us
* Advancing our commercial or economic interests

We do not knowingly sell or share the Personal Information of consumers under 16 years of age. We do not use Sensitive Personal Information for purposes other than those the CCPA and its regulations allow for.

**Retention of Personal Information**  
We retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which we collect it, such as to provide you with the service you have requested, and for the purpose of satisfying any legal, accounting, contractual, or reporting requirements that apply to us.

**Your Rights**  
If you are a California resident, you have the following rights with respect to your Personal Information:

1. The right to know what Personal Information we have collected about you, including the categories of Personal Information, the categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information, the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing Personal Information (if applicable), the categories of third parties to whom we disclose Personal Information (if applicable), and the specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you;
2. The right to delete Personal Information that we collected from you, subject to certain exceptions;
3. The right to correct inaccurate Personal Information that we maintain about you;
4. If we sell or share Personal Information, the right to opt out of the sale or sharing;
5. If we use or disclose sensitive Personal Information for purposes other than those allowed by the CCPA and its regulations, the right to limit our use or disclosure; and
6. The right not to receive discriminatory treatment by us for the exercise of privacy rights the CCPA confers.

_How to Submit a Request to Know, Delete, and/or Correct_  
You may submit a request to know, delete, and/or correct through our interactive webform [available here](https://transdevnaitccpa.powerappsportals.com/CCPA-Form/), by emailing us at [infoUS@transdev.com](mailto:infoUS@transdev.com), or by calling us toll free at 1-800-225-8880.

If you are submitting a request on behalf of a California resident, please submit the request through one of the designated methods discussed above. After submitting the request, we will require additional information to verify your authority to act on behalf of the California resident.

_Our Process for Verifying a Request to Know, Delete, and/or Correct_  
If we determine that your request is not subject to an exemption or exception, we will comply with your request upon verification of your identity and, to the extent applicable, the identity of the California resident on whose behalf you are making such request. We will verify your identity either to a “reasonable degree of certainty” or a “reasonably high degree of certainty” depending on the sensitivity of the Personal Information and the risk of harm to you by unauthorized disclosure, deletion, or correction as applicable.

For requests to access categories of Personal Information and for requests to delete or correct Personal Information that is not sensitive and does not pose a risk of harm by unauthorized deletion or correction, we will verify your identity to a “reasonable degree of certainty” by verifying at least two data points that you previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verifying identities.

For requests to access specific pieces of Personal Information or for requests to delete or correct Personal Information that is sensitive and poses a risk of harm by unauthorized deletion or correction, we will verify your identity to a “reasonably high degree of certainty” by verifying at least three pieces of Personal Information you previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verifying identities. In addition, you must submit a signed declaration under penalty of perjury stating that you are the individual whose Personal Information is being requested.

**Right to Opt Out of Sale or Sharing of Personal Information**  
If you are a California resident, you have the right to direct us to stop selling or sharing your Personal Information.  
You may submit a request to opt out of sales or sharing through our interactive webform available by clicking on this link:  
Cookie Settings  
This will allow you to opt out of sales or sharing on Transdevna.com. If you would like to exercise this opt-out right on one of our other Sites, you can do so by clicking on the “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information” link included in the footer of that Site.

If you have enabled privacy controls on your browser (such as a plugin), we will also treat that as a valid request to opt out. To opt out of our use of third-party advertising Cookies, please see the section “How You Can Opt Out of Cookies” above.

**Shine the Light Law**  
We do not disclose personal information obtained through our Sites or Services to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Accordingly, we have no obligations under California Civil Code § 1798.83.

#### 12\. Accessibility

We are committed to ensuring this Privacy Policy is accessible to individuals with disabilities. If you wish to access this Privacy Policy in an alternative format, please contact us as described below.

#### 13\. How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies or practices, please contact us per below:  
Transdev North America, Inc.  
720 E. Butterfield Road, Ste. 300  
Lombard, Illinois 60148  
1-800-225-8880

[Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information](javascript:showCookieSettings();)   ©2024 Transdev U.S., Inc. All Rights Reserved.

Cookie Settings
